<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="home.xsl"?>

<info>
	<from>1</from>
	<to>18</to>
	<currentPage>1</currentPage>
	<total>18</total>
	<totalPages>1</totalPages>
	<queryTime>0.019</queryTime>
	<totalTime>0.072</totalTime>
	<partial>false</partial>
	<canonicalUrl>/v1/products((categoryPath.id=abcat0507008&amp;customerReviewAverage&gt;=3.5))?show=categoryPath.id,name,regularPrice,salePrice,url,customerReviewAverage,manufacturer,image,longDescription&amp;pageSize=100&amp;format=json&amp;apiKey=hjz08uwA2k6tVBeb71PBHAGB</canonicalUrl>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - ROG CROSSHAIR VI HERO (Socket AM4) USB 3.1 AMD Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>219.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>219.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6239835/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6239/6239835_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Maximize your gaming experience with this Asus Crosshair VI Hero motherboard. Compatibility with AMD X370 Ryzen processors and DDR4 RAM produces epic gameplay, while the Aura Sync LED provides stunning synchronized effects. The hollow heat-sink on this Asus Crosshair VI Hero gaming motherboard allows light from the hub to shine through and allows for maximum heat dissipation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - ROG STRIX H370-F GAMING (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>139.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>139.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6239836/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.2</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6239/6239836_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Maximize your gaming experience with this Asus ROG Strix H370-F gaming motherboard. Compatibility with 8th-generation Intel Core processors and DDR4 RAM produces epic performance, while the Aura Sync LED lighting provides stunning effects. The DIY-friendly design on this Asus ROG Strix H370-F gaming motherboard allows simple PC building and installation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - B450 TOMAHAWK (Socket AM4) USB 3.1 Gen 1 AMD Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>114.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>114.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6305796/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6305/6305796_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Dominate the competition with this MSI Tomahawk gaming motherboard. Plated heat sinks regulate temperature, and the Mystic Light utility's palette lets you pick and personalize your system with 16.8 million colors. This MSI Tomahawk gaming motherboard uses Store MI technology, which maximizes storage and improves performance with an AMD processor and solid-state drive.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MPG Z390 GAMING PLUS (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>149.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>134.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6305798/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6305/6305798_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build the ultimate PC with this MSI MPG Z390 Gaming Plus motherboard. Featuring a premium layout and an extended heat sink design, this motherboard supports high-end multi-core processors and keeps them cool for maximum performance. This MSI MPG Z390 Gaming Plus motherboard enhances data performance with two advanced M.2 slots.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MPG Z390 GAMING EDGE AC (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>184.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6305799/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6305/6305799_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Design the perfect PC with this MSI MPG Z390 Gaming Edge AC motherboard. Featuring two advanced M.2 slots, DDR4-boosting technology and three PCI-e expansion slots, this motherboard accommodates and enhances a variety of high-end components. This MSI MPG Z390 Gaming Edge AC motherboard maximizes processor performance with an optimal layout and a digital power design.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - TUF X470-PLUS GAMING (Socket AM4) USB 3.1 Gen 1 AMD Motherboard</name>
		<regularPrice>170.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>170.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6306007/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6306/6306007_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your PC gaming experience with this ASUS gaming motherboard. It supports up to 64GB of DDR4 SDRAM and AMD processors with speeds up to 3.2GHz so you have smooth, uninterrupted play, and the DTS audio provides positional cues to stereo headphones for more realistic sound. This ASUS gaming motherboard includes electrostatic discharge guards to protect components from damage.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MEG Z390 ACE (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>319.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>319.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6306408/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6306/6306408_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Conquer the battlefield with this MSI MEG Z390 ACE motherboard. Ideal for online gaming, this motherboard ensures low-latency connections with Killer E2500 Gigabit Ethernet connectivity and enhances DDR4 efficiency with shielded DIMM slots for faster performance. This MSI MEG Z390 ACE motherboard _boosts processor performance with an optimal layout and provides an extra burst of speed when you need it with automated overclocking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - X470 GAMING PLUS (Socket AM4) USB 3.1 Gen 1 AMD Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>139.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>134.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6306413/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6306/6306413_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Set the standard with this MSI Gaming Plus motherboard. Included software detects USB devices and improves their performance, and Audio Boost produces studio-level sound quality for exciting game play. The Mystic Light application lets you readily access 16.8 million colors and 10 effects with one click or with your mobile device.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - ROG MAXIMUS XI HERO (WI-FI) (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>289.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>279.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6306415/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6306/6306415_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your gaming rig with this Asus gaming motherboard. Its dedicated onboard clock generator lets you harness its full power, and the ROG firmware provides stability to ensure optimal performance. The cooling system on this Asus gaming motherboard is configured by Fan Xpert 4 and UEFI BIOS to prevent overheating.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - TUF Z390-PLUS GAMING (WI-FI) (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard</name>
		<regularPrice>169.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6311233/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6311/6311233_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Bring your dream PC to life with this ASUS TUF gaming motherboard. It has onboard dual-band Wi-Fi and Bluetooth 5.0 interfaces for built-in wireless connectivity, and Optimem II technology ensures stable modules at overclocking rates. This Intel Optane ASUS memory-ready TUF gaming motherboard is made with military-grade components for heavy-duty performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - ROG Strix B450-F Gaming (Socket AM4) USB 3.1 Gen 2 AMD Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>126.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6311234/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6311/6311234_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Get started on your DIY gamer rig with this ASUS ROG Strix motherboard. Its five-way optimization feature simplifies tuning on CPU performance and cooling, and the two PCIe M.2 slots with RAID support let you install high-performance storage components. This ASUS ROG Strix motherboard has an AM4 socket for your AMD Ryzen processor.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - ROG CROSSHAIR VII HERO (Socket AM4) USB 3.1 Gen 1 AMD Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>279.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>254.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6311236/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6311/6311236_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy building a custom gaming PC with this DIY-friendly ASUS ROG Crosshair motherboard. Its AM4 socket supports AMD Ryzen processors, and the silk screen labels provide easy slot identification for installing modules and other parts. Synchronize this ASUS ROG Crosshair motherboard with Aura Sync components and your Philips Hue lighting for customized illumination.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - ROG STRIX Z390-E GAMING (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>244.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>231.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6311237/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6311/6311237_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build a solid gamer desktop with this ASUS ROG Strix gaming motherboard. It&amp;#8217;s compatible with eighth-generation and ninth-generation Intel Core processors, and its DIY-friendly design consists of pre-mounted I/O shields and a SafeSlot system for easy, secure installation of modules. This ASUS ROG Strix gaming motherboard has onboard dual-band Wi-Fi and Bluetooth 5.0 interfaces for strong wireless connectivity.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - PRIME Z390-A (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard with LED Lighting</name>
		<regularPrice>189.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>189.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6311238/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6311/6311238_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Tailor a high-performance desktop with this ASUS Prime motherboard. Its AI overclocking feature identifies optimal settings for your CPU and cooling system for simplified manual tuning, and the Crystal Sound 3 audio interface with DTS Headphone:X technology supports surround sound formats. This versatile ASUS Prime motherboard lets you control thermal settings via the Fan Xpert 4 or UEFI BIOS application.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MPG Z390 GAMING PRO CARBON AC (Socket LGA1151) USB 3.1 Gen 1 Intel Motherboard</name>
		<regularPrice>239.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>230.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6319405/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6319/6319405_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Take your gaming performance to the next level with this MSi gaming motherboard. Compatible with up to ninth-generation Intel processors, it supports high-performance features like DDR4 RAM and USB Type-C, and the Gaming I/O cover offers enhanced lighting options. This MSi gaming motherboard includes thermal enhancement features for high-speed M.2 storage to provide optimal performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MPG X570 GAMING EDGE WIFI (Socket AM4) USB-C Gen2 AMD Motherboard</name>
		<regularPrice>209.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>209.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6357223/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6357/6357223_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build a powerful PC with this MSI MPG X570 Gaming Edge motherboard. The AM4 socket handles second-generation and third-generation AMD Ryzen processors for smooth gaming performance, while DDR4 Boost supports RAM overclocking and rapid data transfer. This MSI MPG X570 Gaming Edge motherboard features a PCIe 4.0 interface for high-end graphics cards and SSDs, and USB 3.2 technology delivers super-fast transfer speeds.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MPG X570 GAMING PLUS (Socket AM4) USB-C Gen2 AMD Motherboard</name>
		<regularPrice>169.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6357229/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6357/6357229_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build a computer to dominate the competition with this MSI MPG X570 Gaming Plus motherboard. The four DDR4 memory slots accommodate up to 128GB of RAM, while the five PCIe expansion slots offer space for additional components. This MSI MPG X570 Gaming Plus motherboard works with select AMD Ryzen 9 processors for a powerful computing experience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507008</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - MEG X570 ACE (Socket AM4) USB-C Gen2 AMD Motherboard</name>
		<regularPrice>369.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>369.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6357252/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6357/6357252_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Assemble a powerful PC with this MSI MEG X570 ACE motherboard. The three M.2 slots enable installation of high-performance storage components, while the four DDR4 memory slots let you add up to 128GB of RAM for seamless performance. This MSI MEG X570 ACE motherboard is compatible with select AMD Ryzen 9 processors to handle complex applications and programs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 5 1600 Six-Core 3.2 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>189.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>189.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6091101/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6091/6091101_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Bank on solid, efficient computing performance with this six-core AMD Ryzen 5 desktop processor. Its 3.6GHz maximum turbo core speed sufficiently supports 1080p and VR gaming, and its 16MB L3 cache memory provides an enhanced CPU memory operation. The 65W default thermal design power of this AMD Ryzen 5 desktop processor lets you build a power-efficient computer system.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i3-8100 Coffee Lake Quad-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor - Silver</name>
		<regularPrice>119.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>119.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6162970/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6162/6162970_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Increase productivity with this eighth-generation Intel Core i3 processor. Its low power consumption at 65W keeps motherboard components cool, and its 3.60GHz clock speed lets you multitask efficiently on each of the four cores. This Intel Core i3 processor supports up to 64GB of DDR4 RAM to meet future expansion needs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i7-8700 Coffee Lake Six-Core 3.2 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>309.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>309.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6162975/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6162/6162975_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Construct a lightning-fast motherboard with this six-core Intel Core i7 processor. Its 12MB of cache provides fast data retrieval to speed up operations, and its low 65W power consumption keeps components cool. Crank this eighth-generation Intel Core i7 processor up to its turbo frequency of 4.6GHz to run large programs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i7-8700K Coffee Lake Six-Core 3.7 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>379.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>379.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6162997/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6162/6162997_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Use this Intel Core i7 processor to upgrade your current motherboard. Its 3.7GHz base frequency can be overclocked to 4.7GHz for running multiple power-hungry programs over its six cores, and it supports 4K graphics for enjoying movies and games. This Intel Core i7 processor lets you add up to 64GB of DDR4 RAM for powerful multitasking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i5-8600K Coffee Lake Six-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor - Silver</name>
		<regularPrice>259.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>259.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6163018/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6163/6163018_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build your own computer beginning with this Intel Core i5 processor. Its 9MB of cache memory offers fast data retrieval for maximum efficiency, and the base frequency of 3.6GHz powers through demanding applications and programs. Switch between multiple tasks smoothly with this eighth-generation Intel Core i5 processor when you pair it with up to 64GB of DDR4 RAM.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i5-8400 Coffee Lake Six-Core 2.8 GHz Desktop Processor - Silver</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6163019/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6163/6163019_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Supercharge your custom PC with this eighth-generation Intel Core i5 processor. It has six threads and six cores constructed with Intel's Coffee Lake architecture and a 9MB cache to make your computer fast and efficient. This Intel Core i5 processor supports up to 64GB of RAM for extreme multitasking capabilities.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 5 2400G Quad-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>169.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6224300/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6224/6224300_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your custom desktop PC with this 14nm process, quad-core AMD Ryzen 5 processor. It includes 11-core Radeon Vega graphics for higher performance without a separate graphics card, and it works with the AMD Wraith Stealth cooler for effective heat dissipation. This AMD Ryzen 5 processor supports PCIe 3.0 and HDMI to interface with up-to-date hardware and displays.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 7 2700X Octa-Core 3.7 GHz Desktop Processor with Wraith Prism LED Cooler</name>
		<regularPrice>329.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>329.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6224301/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6224/6224301_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build your own motherboard with this AMD Ryzen 7 processor. Its advanced Wraith Prism cooler lets it operate at lower noise volumes for quieter processing, and its clear fan helps keep components cool while providing better RGB light illumination for creating fun effects. This AMD Ryzen 7 processor has eight cores for completing multiple system-intensive tasks at once.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 5 2600 Six-Core 3.4 GHz Desktop Processor with Wraith Stealth Cooler</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6234508/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6234/6234508_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build your own custom motherboard beginning with this AMD Ryzen 5 processor. Its six cores and 12 threads provide powerful processing capability for system-intensive tasks, and its base/boost speed sits at 3.4GHz and 3.9GHz, respectively, for efficient overclocking. This AMD Ryzen 5 processor has a Wraith Stealth cooler to keep components from overheating.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 3 2200G Quad-Core 3.5 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>99.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6234509/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6234/6234509_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Create a compact gamer PC with this quad-core AMD Ryzen 3 desktop processor. Its integrated Radeon Vega 8 graphics support dynamic, high-resolution visuals, and its built-in Wraith Stealth cooler ensures thermal stability. This unlocked AMD Ryzen 3 desktop processor has a 3.7GHz boost clock speed to keep up with intense gaming.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 7 2700 Octa-Core 3.2 GHz Desktop Processor with Wraith Spire LED Cooler</name>
		<regularPrice>309.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>309.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6234511/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6234/6234511_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Get more gaming speed out of your computer with this AMD Ryzen 7 2700 processor. Eight cores and 16 threads combine with the 16MB L3 cache to process huge chunks of data at up to 4.1GHz for maximum performance. This AMD Ryzen 7 2700 processor comes with a Wraith Spire cooler to ensure powerful heat dissipation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i9-9900K Octa-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>529.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>529.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6302019/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6302/6302019_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Complete your computer setup with this Intel Core i9 desktop processor. The hyper-threading technology allows for 16-way multitasking, and eight cores combine with Turbo Boost Technology 2.0 for quick operations. This Intel Core i9 desktop processor supports Optane memory for more efficient loading and increased overall responsiveness with faster access to data.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i5-9600K Six-Core 3.7 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>279.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>279.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6302020/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6302/6302020_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Boost productivity with this ninth-generation Intel Core i5 desktop processor. The 4.6GHz speed is suitable for games and other CPU-intensive applications, and the six cores deliver smooth performance to help you get your work done faster. Pair this Intel Core i5 desktop processor with Intel 300 Series motherboards for Intel Optane memory support.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i7-9700K Octa-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>409.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>409.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6302021/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6302/6302021_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Boost your desktop's performance with this Intel Core processor. The multitasking ability of its eight cores let you increase your productivity, while its frequency of up to 4.9GHz delivers powerful gaming performance. This Intel Core processor has 12MB of cache to improve access rates and provide fast computation for all your tasks.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i9-9900X 10-core 3.5 GHz Desktop Processor with Enhanced Speedstep Technology</name>
		<regularPrice>999.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>999.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6311303/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6311/6311303_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer with this Intel Core i9 processor. Turbo Boost Max Technology 3.0 identifies the two fastest cores to handle your most demanding programs, and its over-clocking feature lets you get the most out of each core. This Intel Core i9 processor lets you work with 360-degree and VR videos in 4K.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Intel - Core i5-9400F Six-Core 2.9 GHz Desktop Processor without Graphics</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>149.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6350570/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Intel</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6350/6350570_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Run high-end programs and games with this Intel Core i5-9400F processor. The six-core design with a max frequency of 4.10GHz handles multiple programs and browser tabs simultaneously for better productivity, while Intel Boot Guard blocks malicious attacks and viruses. This Intel Core i5-9400F processor supports up to 128GB of DDR4 RAM for seamless multitasking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 9 3900X 12-core 3.8 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>499.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>499.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6356274/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6356/6356274_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Improve the performance of your desktop computer with this AMD Ryzen 9 3900X 12-core processor. The 64MB L3 cache queues instructions in the processor, increasing throughput speed, while the 4.6GHz Max Boost clock provides ample power for running intensive applications. This AMD Ryzen 9 3900X 12-core processor has a Wraith Prism cooling system, which lets sensitive components run smoothly.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 5 3600 Six-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6356278/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6356/6356278_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance the performance of your computer with this AMD Ryzen 5 3600 processor. The 4.2GHz Max Boost speed provides extra power for intense processes, and the 32MB L3 cache increases the overall speed by queuing commands in the processor. This AMD Ryzen 5 3600 processor has a Wraith Stealth cooling system, which ensures sensitive components function flawlessly.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507010</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>AMD - Ryzen 3 3200G Quad-Core 3.6 GHz Desktop Processor</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>99.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6356279/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>AMD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6356/6356279_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance the performance of your desktop computer with this AMD Ryzen 3 3200G quad-core processor. The 4GHz Max Boost clock provides ample power for running intensive applications, and 4MB of L3 cache queues commands in the processor quickly. This AMD Ryzen 3 3200G quad-core processor has Radeon Vega 8 graphics for everyday use playing movies or casual games.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Cooler Master - Hyper 212 EVO 120mm CPU Cooling Fan - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>39.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>36.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4923764/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Cooler Master</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4923/4923764_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This Cooler Master Hyper 212 EVO 120mm fan features Continuous Direct Contact technology to help keep your AMD or Intel&amp;#174; processor cool for efficient operation. The sleeve-bearing design enables up to 40,000 hours of use.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX Series 90mm Hard Swap Interchangeable Fan Kit with LED Lighting - Blue</name>
		<regularPrice>19.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>19.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5705516/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5705/5705516_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Handle the extreme performance of your AMD Radeon graphics card with these blue XFX Hard Swap LED fans. They automatically run at optimal performance during intense operation and offer reduced noise with normal loads or when not in use thanks to their zero-dB technology. The tool-free design of these XFX Hard Swap LED fans provides an easy snap-in installation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX Series 90mm Hard Swap Interchangeable Fan Kit with LED Lighting - Red</name>
		<regularPrice>19.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>19.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5705518/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5705/5705518_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Customize your graphics card and keep it cool with these red XFX Hard Swap LED fans. They're compatible with select AMD Radeon RX 400 graphics cards.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX Series 90mm Hard Swap Interchangeable Fan Kit with LED Lighting - White</name>
		<regularPrice>19.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>19.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5705519/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5705/5705519_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Prevent your gaming PC from overheating with this XFX LED fan. Its zero-dB fan system adjust to your gaming needs, speeding up during intense sessions and slowing during downtime, and its interchangeable LED color system lets you match the fan to your PC. Service or replace this XFX LED fan quickly with its HardSwap technology.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Commander PRO Hardware Controller</name>
		<regularPrice>74.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6229603/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6229/6229603_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Mount this CORSAIR Commander PRO module on the outside of your case to closely monitor gaming hardware. It supports up to six fan connectors and four temperature inputs, so you can push your system to its limits and see how it responds. This CORSAIR Commander PRO module lets you manage fan speeds and temperature readings via CORSAIR LINK software.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Cooler Master - Hyper 212 Black Edition 120mm CPU Cooling Fan - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>39.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>33.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6316584/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Cooler Master</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6316/6316584_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Stop your CPU from overheating with this Cooler Master Hyper 212 Black Edition fan. The Silent Driver IC technology keeps noise and power consumption to a minimum, and its four heat pipes effectively dissipate hot air. This Cooler Master Hyper 212 Black Edition fan includes a push-pull configuration to exhaust heat faster.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507007</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat339900050006</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Cooler Master - Hyper 212 RGB Black Edition 120mm CPU Cooling Fan with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>44.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>38.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6316592/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Cooler Master</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6316/6316592_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Prevent overheating with this Cooler Master RGB fan. Four heat pipes provide direct contact to maximize heat dissipation, and it's compatible with Motherboard RGB software so you can change its settings to maximum cooling or silent operating. This Cooler Master RGB fan has an anodized aluminum finish to provide a sleek, polished look.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance Pro Series 32GB (4PK x 8GB) 1.6 GHz DDR3 DIMM Desktop Memory Kit - Multi</name>
		<regularPrice>189.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>172.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1655374/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1655/1655374_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Add 32GB of DDR3 DIMM memory to your desktop with this Corsair Vengeance Pro Series pack that includes four 8GB modules with 8-layer PCBs and ICs to promote stable overclocking. The anodized-aluminum heat spreaders help keep components cool.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance Pro Series 16GB (2PK x 8GB) 1.6 GHz DDR3 DIMM Desktop Memory Kit - Multi</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>88.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1655416/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1655/1655416_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your desktop's performance with this Corsair Vengeance Pro Series pack, which includes two 8GB DDR3 DIMM memory modules with 8-layer PCBs and Ics to enhance overclocking capabilities. The anodized-aluminum heat spreaders promote cool operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - 8GB (2PK x 4GB) 1.0GHz DDR3 SoDIMM Laptop Memory Kit - Green</name>
		<regularPrice>42.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>42.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/2824528/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/2824/2824528_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This 8GB memory kit is designed for Apple&amp;#174; iMac&amp;#174;, MacBook&amp;#174; and MacBook Pro and features up to 1.0GHz operating speed for easy Web browsing and efficient operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - Performance 4GB (1PK 4GB) 1.6GHz DDR3 Laptop Memory - Green</name>
		<regularPrice>44.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>44.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/3779273/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/3779/3779273_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Keep your notebook moving with this PNY 4GB DDR3 RAM stick. The low 1300MHz frequency speed helps to reduce temperatures across the laptop while ensuring it still has enough speed to keep data flowing to important programs. Each PNY 4GB DDR3 RAM stick is ideal for motherboards that have 1.5-volt RAM slots.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - 8GB 1.6 GHz DDR3 SoDIMM Laptop Memory - Green</name>
		<regularPrice>54.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>54.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4680400/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4680/4680400_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your computer a much-needed upgrade with this PNY 8GB DDR3 RAM. It's designed to fit in a compatible notebook or laptop, and the 1600MHz frequency speed ensures data can quickly be transferred to the stick to reduce or even eliminate delays. This PNY 8GB DDR3 RAM is compatible with 1.35-volt motherboard RAM slots.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - ValueSelect 16GB (2PK x 8GB) 1.3 GHz DDR3 SDRAM Laptop Memory - Multi</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4690376/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4690/4690376_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>ValueSelect is a full line of standard DDR2 and DDR3 memory upgrade kits for home and office desktop and notebook PCs. They are carefully screened by Corsair for reliable operation and backed by our lifetime warranty.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - 16 GB (2PK x 8GB) 1.6 GHz DDR3L SoDIMM Laptop Memory Kit - Green</name>
		<regularPrice>169.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4830503/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4830/4830503_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer's performance by adding more power and RAM with this PNY memory kit. Easily add 16GB of DDR3 RAM to your notebook PC with two separate 8GB parts. The 1600 MHz memory speed helps achieve fast computing, while the lower power consumption in this PNY memory kit saves money and energy.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - Anarchy 16GB (2PK x 8GB) 2.4 GHz DDR4 DIMM Desktop Memory Kit - Blue</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4842608/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4842/4842608_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power up your computer with this PNY 16GB DDR4 RAM stick. The high-performance 2400MHz memory delivers plenty of bandwidth and low latency across all your applications, and the low 1.2-volt draw keeps thermal shock down. Peak performance ensures this PNY 16GB DDR4 RAM stick delivers plenty of gaming fun for longer.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 16GB (2PK x 8GB) 3.2 GHz DDR4 DRAM Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>79.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>79.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895506/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895506_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your computer a performance boost with this Corsair Vengeance LPX DDR4 DRAM desktop memory, which offers high frequencies and bandwidth with low power consumption. XMP 2.0 support enables simple automatic overclocking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 16GB (2PK x 8GB) 2.6 GHz DDR4 DRAM Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>69.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>69.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895508/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895508_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your computer a memory boost with this Corsair Vengeance LPX DDR4 DRAM desktop memory, which offers high frequencies and bandwidth with reduced power consumption. XMP 2.0 support enables simple automatic overclocking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 32GB (2PK x 16GB) 2.6 GHz DDR4 DRAM Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>134.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>134.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895510/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895510_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your computer a boost with this Corsair Vengeance LPX DDR4 DRAM desktop memory, which offers high frequencies and bandwidth while maintaining low power consumption. The up to 2666MHz operating speed ensures smooth, reliable use.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 32GB (2PK x 16GB) 3.2 GHz DDR4 DRAM Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>154.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>154.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895530/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895530_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Boost your computer's memory with this Corsair Vengeance LPX DDR4 DRAM desktop memory, which offers high frequencies and bandwidth with low power consumption. XMP 2.0 support enables simple automatic overclocking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - Performance 16GB (2PK 8GB) 1.6GHz DDR3 Desktop Memory - Green</name>
		<regularPrice>169.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5333202/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5333/5333202_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Accomplish more on your PC with these PNY desktop DIMM modules, which have a clock frequency of 1600MHz. The DDR3 sticks have a combined capacity of 16GB to let you load and utilize more applications at the same time. These PNY desktop DIMM modules have excellent thermal performance to prevent overheating.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - 8GB 1.6 GHz DDR3 DIMM Desktop Memory - Green</name>
		<regularPrice>54.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>54.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5429091/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5429/5429091_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your computer a boost with this PNY 8GB DDR3 desktop RAM. It's ideal for use with various motherboards within desktop computers, and it provides an instant boost or is ideal for replacing fried sticks. The 1600MHz clock speed ensures this PNY 8GB DDR3 desktop RAM gets your computer moving data efficiently.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - 16 GB (2PK x 8GB) 1.8 GHz DDR3 DIMM Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>189.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>189.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5429124/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5429/5429124_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Boost your desktop's performance with this PNY memory kit, which contains two 8GB PC3-14900 CAS 10 DDR3 DIMM modules that operate at up to 1866MHz.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LED Series 32GB (4PK 8GB) 2.666GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory with LED Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>309.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>309.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5580492/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5580/5580492_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Corsair Vengeance memory modules are designed with overclockers in mind. Vengeance DIMMs are built using RAM specially selected for their high-performance potential. Aluminum heat spreaders help dissipate heat, and provide the aggressive look that you want in your gaming rig.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LED 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.2GHz PC4-25600 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>149.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>149.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5580495/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5580/5580495_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your computer a performance boost with this Corsair Vengeance memory kit. Each if its two 8GB memory module has 10-layer printed circuit boards for improved signal routing and faster CAD rendering. This 16GB Corsair Vengeance memory kit has a speed of 3200MHz to meet the overclocking requirements of your gaming system.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LED 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3GHz PC4-24000 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>209.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>209.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5580497/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5580/5580497_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Boost your gaming rig with this Corsair Vengeance memory kit. It has pre-configured XMP 2.0 profiles that provide automatic overclocking settings to match the performance requirements of your gaming system. This 16GB Corsair Vengeance memory kit works with 3000Mhz speeds and low voltages for fast performance at lower power consumption.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance 16 GB (2PK x 8GB) 1.6 GHz DDR3 DIMM Desktop Memory Kit - Multi</name>
		<regularPrice>147.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>138.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5771735/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5771/5771735_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This 2-pack of Corsair Vengeance 8GB DDR3 memory delivers enhanced multitasking performance for your 2nd or 3rd Generation Intel&amp;#174; Core&amp;#8482; dual-channel processor- and motherboard-equipped desktop.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LPX Series 32GB (2PK 16GB) 3.0GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>144.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>144.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822461/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822461_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build a powerful yet efficient gaming rig with this 32GB Corsair VENGEANCE memory kit. Its XMP 2.0 support for automatic overclocking on its two 16GB DDR4 modules lets it keep up with intense multitasking demands while operating with low-voltage output. The anodized aluminum heat spreader on this 3000MHz Corsair VENGEANCE LPX memory kit keeps its cool.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LPX Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.0GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - White</name>
		<regularPrice>74.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822462/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822462_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy high-performance games and applications with this 16GB Corsair Vengeance memory kit. The pure aluminum heat spreaders on this dual pack of DDR4 memory enable trouble-free overclocking for Intel X99 or 100 Series motherboards. The low-profile design of this Corsair Vengeance memory kit is great for smaller computers with limited space.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LPX Series 32GB (2PK 16GB) 2.133GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822464/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822464_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Run your gaming computer with optimum performance and efficiency by using this 32GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE memory kit. Its XMP 2.0 support provides automatic overclocking, and its pure aluminum heat spreader maintains a thermally stable operation. The two 16GB DDR4 modules of this CORSAIR VENGEANCE memory kit are compatible with Intel X99 motherboards.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LPX Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.2GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - White</name>
		<regularPrice>79.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>79.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822465/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822465_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Handle high-bandwidth overclocking demands with this 16GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit. Its two 8GB modules provide high-speed operation of up to 3200MHz, and it automatically adjusts overclocking performance with its XMP 2.0 support. The DDR4 form factor of this CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit runs efficiently with Intel X99 and 100 Series motherboards.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LPX Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.0GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>74.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>72.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822467/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822467_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Increase your overclocking performance with this 16GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit. Its DDR4 form factor provides low-voltage operation for lower energy consumption and optimal compatibility with Intel X99 and 100 Series motherboards. This CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit consists of two 8GB modules, and it stays thermally stable with its pure aluminum heat spreader.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LPX Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 2.4GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>67.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>67.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822470/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822470_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Drive your high-performance gaming rig with this 16GB Corsair Vengeance LPX memory kit. It consists of two 8GB modules, and its XMP 2.0 support provides automatic overclocking for efficient operation with Intel X99 and 100 motherboards. This DDR4-form-factor Corsair Vengeance LPX memory kit runs with low power consumption at 1.2V.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - DOMINATOR PLATINUM 32GB (2PK 16GB) 3.0GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory with DHX cooling - Black/silver</name>
		<regularPrice>174.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>174.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5822471/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5822/5822471_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Unleash full overclocking power with this 3000MHz Corsair Dominator Platinum memory kit. It's optimized for handling intense bandwidth activity with Intel's X99 and 100 series motherboards, and its aluminum heat spreader with patented DHX cooling technology provides efficient thermal management. This 32GB Corsair Dominator Platinum memory kit includes two 16GB DDR4 modules.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE LED Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 2.4GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory with LED Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5823005/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5823/5823005_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer's overall performance with this CORSAIR VENGEANCE DDR4 memory. The bold LED lighting and precision engineered light bar add to the look of gaming computer designs, and superior overclocking ensures speedy performance. This CORSAIR VENGEANCE DDR4 is compatibility tested for flawless use with the latest Intel X99, 100, 200 and AMD Ryzen Series gaming motherboards.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE RGB Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.0GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>109.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>108.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5823006/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5823/5823006_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Maximize the overclocking potential of your gaming system with this 16GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE RGB memory kit. Its anodized aluminum heat spreader provides efficient thermal performance, and its low-voltage DDR4 form factor is compatible with Intel 100 and 200 series motherboards. This CORSAIR VENGEANCE RGB memory kit meets your automatic overclocking requirements with its preconfigured XMP 2.0 profiles.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - Anarchy-X 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.2GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory - Red</name>
		<regularPrice>209.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>209.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5878702/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5878/5878702_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer to handle high-action gaming titles with this PNY Anarchy system memory. Boosting your setup to 16GB DDR4, the easy-to-install card lets you multitask across several platforms without missing a beat. Anarchy X heat spreaders pull heat away from delicate components for reliable speed, and this PNY Anarchy system memory is compatible with Windows 10 and higher.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE RGB Series 32GB (4PK 8GB) 3.6GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>454.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>454.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5901975/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5901/5901975_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer with this this CORSAIR VENGEANCE memory kit. The 32GB of RAM ensures fast multitasking and efficient program execution, and this stick supports RGB lighting for customized builds. This Corsair Vengeance memory kit is compatible with the CORSAIR LINK app, so you can monitor temperature and performance from your device.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 4GB 2.4GHz PC4-19200 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>22.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>22.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5989002/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5989/5989002_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience smoother computer operation with this 4GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory stick. Its 2400Mhz speed facilitates faster performance, and the anodized aluminum heat spreader provides efficient thermal management to prevent overheating. Install this dual-channel CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory stick in pairs to get a total of 8GB for system stability.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE Series 16GB (2PK 8GB) 2.4GHz DDR4 Laptop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>69.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>69.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6063100/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6063/6063100_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Increase the reliability and performance of your laptop with this CORSAIR DDR4 memory kit. It includes two 8GB memory modules, so you can multitask between programs smoothly, and they seamlessly integrate with sixth-generation Intel Core systems. This CORSAIR DDR4 memory kit runs at 2400MHz, so you can accomplish more tasks in a shorter period.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - VENGEANCE RGB Series 32GB (2PK 16GB) 3.2GHz DDR4 Desktop Memory with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>269.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>269.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6063200/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6063/6063200_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Optimize overclocking performance with this 32GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE memory kit. Its 3200MHz speed provides powerful support for high-bandwidth multitasking and intense gaming, and it has built-in heat spreaders for thermal stability. The two 16GB modules of this CORSAIR VENGEANCE memory kit have XMP 2.0 support for automatic clock speed setting.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3GHz PC4-24000 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Cool Gray</name>
		<regularPrice>74.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6247250/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6247/6247250_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Unleash the overclocking potential of your gaming rig with this 16GB Corsair Vengeance LPX memory kit. The pure aluminum build offers efficient heat management, and the compact module design is customized to fit smaller spaces. The DDR4 form factor of this Corsair Vengeance LPX memory kit provides great bandwidth with reduced power consumption.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance RGB PRO 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.2GHz PC4-25600 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>94.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>94.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6256216/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6256/6256216_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Light up your computer with this CORSAIR Vengeance RGB PRO DDR4 RAM. It comes as two 8GB sticks so that you get 16GB to hammer through games, and each stick has RGB LEDs that glow and can be controlled from your computer. Each stick of 3200MHz CORSAIR Vengeance RGB PRO DDR4 RAM is carefully selected and screened for high overclocking potential.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 8GB (2PK 4GB) 2.4GHz PC4-19200 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>44.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>44.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6256217/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6256/6256217_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your desktop PC with this 8GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit. It comes in two 4GB modules, and the eight-layer PCB and pure aluminum heat spreader ensure optimal cooling to support high-performance overclocking. The DDR4 form factor of this 2400MHz CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit provides fast responses and power-efficient operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 8GB 2.4GHz PC4-19200 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>36.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>34.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6256218/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6256/6256218_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Improve the performance of your PC with this 8GB CORSAIR Vengeance LPX memory stick. This DDR4 RAM has powerful temporary storage capabilities, letting you run applications and play games with shorter loading times. This CORSAIR Vengeance LPX memory stick can be paired with another of its kind for better results.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 16GB (2PK 8GB) 2.133GHz PC4-17000 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>67.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>67.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6256219/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6256/6256219_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your gaming PC a boost with this 16GB CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit. The two DDR4 RAM sticks deliver impressive temporary data storage for faster performance, and the pure aluminum build facilitates rapid heat dissipation to prevent overheating. This CORSAIR VENGEANCE LPX memory kit is compatible with most motherboards.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance RGB PRO 16GB (2PK 8GB) 2.666GHz PC4-21300 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>84.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>84.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6256221/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6256/6256221_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Blast through your favorite games or heavy-duty programs with this CORSAIR Vengeance RGB PRO DDR4 RAM. It comes as two sticks so that it's easy to install on suitable 288-pin motherboards, and ultra-bright RGB LEDs let you customize the glow in your PC. Tight screening makes this CORSAIR Vengeance RGB PRO DDR4 RAM ideal for overclocking from its native 2666MHz speed.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance RGB PRO 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3GHz PC4-24000 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6256222/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6256/6256222_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Get the most out of your gaming PC with this 16GB CORSAIR Vengeance RGB DDR4 RAM. Each of the 8GB sticks snaps into your compatible motherboard, providing a total of 16GB, and extreme performance is assured thanks to the 3000 MHz frequency. Installation is simple thanks to the plug-and-play nature of this CORSAIR Vengeance RGB DDR4 RAM.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 8GB (2PK 4GB) 3GHz PC4-24000 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>44.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>44.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6317294/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6317/6317294_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Increase your computer's running speed with this Corsair VENGEANCE LPX DDR4 memory kit. Its eight-layer PBC and carefully screened ICs are supported by a pure aluminum heat spreader that offers fast, even dissipation to extend its overall overclocking potential. This Corsair VENGEANCE LPX DDR4 memory kit contains two 4GB modules in a low-profile design that's compatible with smaller cases.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance LPX 32GB (2PK 16GB) 2.4GHz PC4-19200 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6319885/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6319/6319885_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Achieve peak overclocking performance with this 32GB Corsair Vengeance LPX memory kit. Unique aluminum heat spreaders keep the DDR4 modules cool under pressure, and XMP 2.0 ensures you get reliable performance without any lockups. This Corsair Vengeance LPX memory kit has a small form factor, so it fits inside slimmer cases.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance RGB PRO 32GB (2PK 16GB) 3GHz PC4-24000 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>159.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>159.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6319887/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6319/6319887_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your gaming PC with this Corsair Vengeance RGB Pro memory kit. It has two 16GB DDR4 memory sticks that add up to 32GB of RAM to boost performance, and the dynamic RGB lighting shows through tower vents and transparent side panels for ambience. This Corsair Vengeance RGB Pro memory kit reduces load times for seamless game play.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Vengeance RGB PRO 32GB (2PK 16GB) 3.2GHz PC4-25600 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>169.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6333800/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6333/6333800_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Improve your gaming experience with this 32GB of Corsair Vengeance RGB Pro DDR4 desktop memory. Optimized on the latest motherboards, this desktop memory provides the bandwidth and response times to accelerate PC and gaming performance. This Corsair Vengeance RGB Pro DDR4 desktop memory has 10 RGB LEDs per module and lets you use the Corsair iCUE software to customize and synchronize lighting.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Dominator Platinum RGB 32GB (4PK 8GB) 3.2GHz PC4-25600 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>259.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>259.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6337722/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6337/6337722_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Ensure a smooth gaming and work experience with this Corsair Dominator Platinum 32GB DDR4 RAM memory kit. With 32GB of memory, there's plenty of resources to run a host of intensive games and other applications at the same time. This Corsair Dominator Platinum 32GB DDR4 RAM memory kit features LEDs for a stylish appearance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Dominator Platinum RGB 16GB (2PK 8GB) 3.2GHz PC4-25600 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit with RGB Lighting - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6337726/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>3.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6337/6337726_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Speed up computers with this Corsair Dominator Platinum 16GB DDR4 memory kit. Rated at 3000Mhz, each 8GB stick ensures quick command processing while multitasking, and the heat spreader maintains optimal temperatures for reliable operation. This Corsair Dominator Platinum 16GB DDR4 memory kit has ample overclocking headroom for excellent performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - Dominator Platinum RGB 32GB (2PK 16GB) 3.2GHz PC4-25600 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>219.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>217.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6337727/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6337/6337727_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience faster computing performance with 32GB of Corsair Dominator Platinum RGB DDR4 memory. Speeds of up to 3200MHz enable quick response times, while dual cooling ensures optimal operating temperatures for reliable performance. This Corsair Dominator Platinum RGB DDR4 memory is easy to install and compatible with a number of Intel and AMD motherboards.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - XLR8 16GB (2PK 8GB) 2.666GHz PC4-21300 DDR4 DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Desktop Memory Kit - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>104.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>104.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6346309/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6346/6346309_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade system performance with this 16GB PNY desktop memory set. The two 8GB RAM sticks support dual channel mode for increased memory bandwidth. DDR4 technology offers reduced power consumption and fast data transfer rates for improved performance. This 2666MHz PNY desktop memory set has a black-and-red design for easy identification.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0506002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - 8GB 2.4GHz PC4-19200 DDR4 SO-DIMM Unbuffered Non-ECC Laptop Memory - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6346312/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6346/6346312_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Improve your PC's response time during intensive tasks with this PNY DDR4 2400MHz notebook memory. The 2400MHz RAM frequency and DDR4 technology offer fast speeds, high bandwidth and enhanced thermal performance. This PNY DDR4 2400MHz notebook memory comes as an 8GB stick for easy upgrading and replacement in various PCs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>HGST - Travelstar 5K1000 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1578004/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>HGST</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1578/1578004_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>House plenty of files on your Windows or Mac laptop by installing this HGST Travelstar 5K1000 0J22413 internal SATA hard drive, which features a 1TB capacity for ample storage. Speeds up to 998MB/sec. promote rapid data transfer.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Red 1TB Internal SATA NAS Hard Drive (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>68.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>68.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1765078/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1765/1765078_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Expand your network storage with this 1TB WD Red WD10JFCX internal hard drive, which runs at a low temperature for added reliability. The drive reduces data loss by completing the command in process before shutting down in the event of a power failure.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 750GB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Laptops (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/2399001/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/2399/2399001_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Store your favorite photos, music, films and more on this WD Blue WD7500BPVXSP internal hard drive, which features 750GB of space. NoTouch Ramp Load technology and StableTrac technology offer reliability in your laptop.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Red 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>149.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>128.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/2452034/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/2452/2452034_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This WD Red WD40EFRX internal hard drive is designed for NAS systems with 1-8 drive bays in both 3.5" form factors. Its 4TB capacity provides plenty of space to house files, and the Serial ATA interface lets you connect your laptop or desktop.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Black 2TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>119.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>119.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/3055346/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/3055/3055346_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This WD Black WD2003FZEX internal hard drive safeguards up to 2TB of digital data with Corruption Protection technology, which limits data loss during a power failure. StableTrac technology reduces system-induced vibrations for increased performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Black 1TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>72.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>72.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/3055382/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.2</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/3055/3055382_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This WD Black WD1003FZEX SATA internal hard drive provides 1TB of storage, so you can easily house plenty of pictures, videos, music and other important files on your Windows or Mac desktop.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Black 500GB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>52.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>52.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/3530928/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/3530/3530928_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Add power to your computing with this WD 500GB internal hard drive, which is ideal for everything from graphics to gaming. Made for compatibility with 2.5-inch SATA 6 ports, this drive offers fast dual transfer rates for reliable power. The 32 MB cache on this WD 500GB internal hard drive provides dependable performance no matter the task.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 500GB Internal SATA Hard Drive</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>48.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4830705/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4830/4830705_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build extra application space into your laptop with this WD Blue internal hard drive, featuring 6 GB/s transfers speeds for reliable performance. The low-power-consumption design gives you more freedom to run your applications without worrying about eating up battery life, and this WD Blue internal hard drive features noise-reducing technology for seamless, quiet integration.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 500GB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>47.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4842401/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4842/4842401_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Beef up your desktop or laptop computer's performance with this WD Blue internal hard drive. The upgrade is simple, using Acronis True Image WD edition software, and the 6 GB/s transfer speed offers reliable power for running your applications. This WD Blue internal hard drive features NoTouch Ramp Load technology, extending the life of the recording head.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - NAS 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>134.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>134.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5067800/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5067/5067800_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Add extra storage to your network attached storage with this Western Digital 4TB NAS hard drive. It is designed to cope with the demands placed on it by your NAS system, and it's extremely energy efficient to reduce your overall energy consumption. The Western Digital 4TB NAS hard drive seamlessly integrates with your system.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Surveillance 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>64.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>64.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5193300/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5193/5193300_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Provide ample storage space for your security camera footage with this WD surveillance storage hard drive. This storage device provides support for up to 32 HD cameras, keeping all your footage ready for reference as needed. Featuring Allframe technology, this WD surveillance storage hard drive reduces frame loss for crisp, precise playback.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Surveillance 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>139.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>139.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5193303/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5193/5193303_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Back up your security camera footage with this WD surveillance retail kit. The IntelliSeek technology lowers power consumption to deliver long-lasting use in your computer, and the optimized design supports up to eight drives and 32 HD cameras. Featuring 4TB of storage, this WD surveillance retail kit stores your footage for convenient playback.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>119.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>101.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5537810/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5537/5537810_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Boost the capabilities of your all-in-one PC or laptop with this WD Blue internal hard drive. The standard 3.5-inch form factor integrates easily with your motherboard, and 4 TB storage offers ample space for games, video libraries and massive quantities of data. This WD Blue internal hard drive features Ramp Load technology to extend the life of the recording head.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 500GB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5552300/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5552/5552300_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Work or game with the reliable capacity of this WD Blue PC hard drive, featuring NoTouch Ramp Load technology to protect your data. With a larger capacity drive, this internal hard drive offers dependable storage and performance for games or graphic work. This WD Blue PC hard drive uses lower power consumption for longer operating times.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Toshiba - 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>119.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5622845/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Toshiba</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5622/5622845_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Add 4TB of storage space to your computer with this Toshiba internal hard drive. Ramp-loading and drive-stabilization technology provide durability to keep your data safe. Its 6-Gbps interface supports fast, uninterrupted data transfers. This Toshiba internal hard drive has Native Command Queuing support for increased performance with a reduced mechanical workload.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Toshiba - 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5622846/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Toshiba</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5622/5622846_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your desktop PC with this Toshiba internal hard drive. Its 1TB capacity offers plenty of storage space for your data, while the 7200 rpm operating speed delivers blazing performance. This Toshiba internal hard drive supports the SATA 3.0 interface to deliver file transfer rates of up to 6 Gbps.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Toshiba - 6TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>191.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>172.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5622854/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Toshiba</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5622/5622854_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer's storage space with this Toshiba desktop internal hard drive. It has a capacity of 6TB and a SATA 3.0 interface that transfers information at 6 Gbps. Native Command Queuing technology delivers a higher level of performance and reduced wear and tear on this Toshiba desktop internal hard drive for greater reliability.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5638723/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5638/5638723_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Secure important documents and high-resolution files with this Western Digital Blue PC hard drive. Its NoTouch ramp load technology keeps the recording head in a safe position off the disk surface to prevent drive damage and protect stored data. This 1TB Western Digital Blue PC hard drive optimizes read operations with its 64MB cache memory.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 3TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>91.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>91.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5638726/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5638/5638726_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Keep precious files safe and accessible with this Western Digital Blue PC hard drive. Its IntelliSeek function reduces power use, noise and vibration by calculating the most efficient seek speeds. With its 5400 rpm SATA III interface and 6 Gbps bandwidth, this 3TB Western Digital Blue PC hard drive provides fast, efficient read and write performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 6TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>214.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>183.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5638729/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5638/5638729_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Store a library of files on your desktop with this Western Digital Blue hard drive. It stores up to 6TB of data and has a SATA 6 Gbps interface for high-speed performance. This Western Digital Blue hard drive uses IntelliSeek technology to increase its reliability by reducing both power consumption and vibration.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Red Pro 2TB Internal SATA NAS Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>134.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>118.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5638732/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5638/5638732_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Invest in high-performance data storage for your business with this Western Digital Red NAS hard drive. Its exclusive NASware 3.0 technology guards your business information with reliable error recovery controls. This 2TB Western Digital Red NAS hard drive protects multi-drive bays against vibration and damage from heavy operations with its multi-axis shock sensor.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - FireCuda 1TB Internal SATA Hybrid Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>84.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5657968/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5657/5657968_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy both speed and high capacity with this 1TB Seagate FireCuda solid state hybrid drive. It has a SATA interface for compatibility with portable enclosures, and it uses flash memory for speeds up to 190MB/sec. and an average seek time of 8.5 ms. This Seagate FireCuda solid state hybrid drive uses power efficiently, resulting in less heat and better performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Enterprise Capacity 3.5 HDD V.5 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>163.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>136.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5657971/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5657/5657971_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Protect important information with this enterprise-class 2TB Seagate internal hard drive. It uses a SATA III interface to provide speedy transfer rates of up to 215 MB/sec., and plug-and-play connectivity makes installation easy, even in RAID setups. The 7200 rpm spindle speed ensures rapid responses when reading data from this Seagate internal hard drive.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - FireCuda 2TB Internal SATA Hybrid Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>109.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>106.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5657978/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5657/5657978_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy blazing speeds with this Seagate FireCuda solid-state hybrid drive. It's made specifically for gaming, so it boots quicker, loads applications more rapidly and responds up to five times faster than standard 7200 rpm drives. This Seagate FireCuda solid-state hybrid drive holds up to 2TB of files, and it's just as useful for creative professionals as it is for gamers.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - IronWolf 10TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>469.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>312.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5707119/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5707/5707119_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Store precious digital data securely on this Seagate IronWolf internal hard drive. Its massive 10TB capacity holds an enormous number of files, and the 180TB/year workload rating lets the drive easily handle multiple users and large data transfers. The 256MB cache in this Seagate IronWolf internal hard drive provides rapid data processing.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Barracuda 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>55.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>43.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5707124/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5707/5707124_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your computer's storage with this 1TB Seagate BarraCuda hard drive. It has a SATA 3 interface to boost burst performance and a 7200 rpm spindle speed to provide fast access to the drive's data. The maximum transfer rate of 210MB/sec. ensures this Seagate BarraCuda hard drive responds rapidly to data requests.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Barracuda Pro 6TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>318.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>239.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5707131/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5707/5707131_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Store your movies, music and documents on this Seagate BarraCuda Pro internal hard drive. It has a maximum sustained transfer speed of 220MB/sec. for fast, dependable data retrieval, making it ideal for creative professionals and business data users. This 6TB Seagate BarraCuda Pro internal hard drive fits 3.5-inch enclosures for easy use in servers and desktops.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - SkyHawk Surveillance HDD 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>86.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5707133/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5707/5707133_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Keep your security system at the ready with this Seagate SkyHawk internal hard drive. Built specifically for surveillance, it holds up to 2TB of video and has Image Perfect firmware to provide crisp images for continuously recording CCTV setups. This Seagate SkyHawk internal hard drive can sustain data transfer rates of up to 180MB/sec. for rapid data retrieval.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - NAS 6TB Internal SATA NAS Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5723344/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5723/5723344_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build a robust shared storage system with this Western Digital Red NAS hard drive. Its NASware 3.0 technology provides for reliable performance in purpose-built NAS systems and RAID environments, and its error-recovery controls secure shared files against system failures. This 6TB Western Digital Red NAS hard drive is suitable for installation within up to eight drive bays.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Black Performance 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>74.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5792406/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5792/5792406_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Store edited photos and videos on this 3.5-inch Western Digital hard drive. It has dynamic cache for optimizing allocation between reads and writes, and there&amp;#8217;s plenty of space to store files with its 1TB capacity. This Western Digital hard drive has data transfer rates up to 6 Gbps for efficient performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Guardian BarraCuda 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>52.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5795713/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5795/5795713_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Save more files and access them quickly with this 1TB Seagate BarraCuda hard drive. Its 140MB/sec. data transfer rate makes moving and downloading files fast and easy, and its slim design adds almost no weight to your computer. This Seagate BarraCuda hard drive is only 7mm thick and can fit into thin laptops.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Guardian BarraCuda 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>98.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>98.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5858301/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5858/5858301_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>BarraCuda leads the industry with the highest capacities for desktops and mobile computers. The uncompromising BarraCuda Pro marries industry-leading storage capacity with 5,400-RPM spin speeds for snappy performance and load times when gaming or performing heavy workloads.Get the most out of your storage with BarraCuda hard drives. From computers full of photos and memories to gaming PCs that need more room to play, BarraCuda grows with you.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Barracuda 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>84.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>84.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6164931/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6164/6164931_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Ensure reliable data storage with this 2TB Seagate BarraCuda internal hard-disk drive. Its 2.5-inch form factor is suitable for laptops and all-in-one PCs, and its SATA III 6 Gbps interface and 128MB cache let you transfer files smoothly at up to 140MB/sec. The Multi-Tier Caching Technology of this Seagate BarraCuda internal hard-disk drive optimizes data flow for faster memory performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - FireCuda 2TB Internal SATA Hybrid Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>99.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6164932/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6164/6164932_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Increase the storage capacity of your desktop or workstation with this Seagate FireCuda hard drive. Its 2TB file capacity provides plenty of room for holding photos, games and documents, and the 8GB of solid-state cache delivers quick access to frequently used data. This Seagate FireCuda hard drive has a SATA III interface for running at speeds up to 6 Gbps.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Barracuda 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>99.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6164933/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6164/6164933_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Increase PC storage with this Seagate BarraCuda 4TB hard drive. Its 3.5-inch form factor installs smoothly into your desktop or all-in-one PC, and the SATA III interface provides fast operating speeds at 6 Gbps. This Seagate BarraCuda 4TB hard drive is highly reliable thanks to its rating of 300,000 load/unload cycles.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Barracuda 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6164934/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6164/6164934_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Load multiple files and applications on your laptop smoothly with this 1TB Seagate BarraCuda internal hard-disk drive. Its 128MB cache with Multi-Tier Caching Technology provides faster data performance, and its 2.5-inch profile is also compatible with all-in-one and slim PCs. The SATA III 6 Gbps interface of this Seagate BarraCuda internal hard-disk drive enables efficient transfer speeds up to 140MB/sec.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - FireCuda 1TB Internal SATA Hybrid Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6164936/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6164/6164936_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Optimize storage performance for your gaming computer with this 1TB Seagate FireCuda internal hybrid drive. Its solid-state cache and SATA III 6 Gbps interface provide efficient data transfers up to 140MB/sec., and it saves on power consumption thanks to its green hybrid technology. The 2.5-inch profile of this Seagate FireCuda internal hybrid drive is also suitable for workstation desktop PCs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops with NoTouch Ramp Load Technology</name>
		<regularPrice>84.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>84.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6220725/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6220/6220725_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your laptop with this 2.5-inch Western Digital 2TB SATA internal hard drive. Its dual processor has a dynamic cache to speed up read and write times, while a 5400 rpm drive speed ensures efficient performance. This Western Digital 2TB SATA internal hard drive maintains a space between the recording head and the disk to reduce wear.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Samsung - Geek Squad Certified Refurbished 970 EVO 250GB Internal PCI Express 3.0 x4 (NVMe) SSD for Laptops with V-NAND Technology</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>39.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6315437/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Samsung</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6315/6315437_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Geek Squad&amp;#174; Certified Refurbished products are thoroughly, painstakingly and lovingly tested, so you can be sure that your device will work right, right away. Learn more about Geek Squad&amp;#174; Certified Refurbished products.Run programs faster with this Samsung 970 EVO 250GB SSD. The NVMe interface utilizes minimal power and offers increased bandwidth for better performance, and read speeds up to 3300 Mbps provide rapid data access. This Samsung 970 EVO 250GB SSD includes management software, providing optimization tools and automatic firmware updates for simple maintenance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Samsung - Geek Squad Certified Refurbished 970 EVO 500GB Internal PCI Express 3.0 x4 (NVMe) SSD for Laptops with V-NAND Technology</name>
		<regularPrice>149.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6315438/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Samsung</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6315/6315438_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Geek Squad&amp;#174; Certified Refurbished products are thoroughly, painstakingly and lovingly tested, so you can be sure that your device will work right, right away. Learn more about Geek Squad&amp;#174; Certified Refurbished products.Increase system performance with this Samsung EVO NVMe internal SSD. Sequential read speeds of up to 3400 Mbps and sequential write speeds up to 2300 Mbps ensure quick file access, while the 500GB capacity provides ample data storage. This Samsung EVO NVMe internal SSD features overheating protection technology to maintain optimal temperatures for reliable performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Blue 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6331502/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6331/6331502_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>With a Serial ATA interface, this WD Blue WD10EZEXSP internal hard drive easily connects to your PC or Mac. The 1TB capacity offers ample space to house important files, such as pictures, videos and music.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Toshiba - L200 Laptop PC 1TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Laptops with Advanced Format Technology</name>
		<regularPrice>47.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>47.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6333392/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Toshiba</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6333/6333392_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Expand data storage capacities with this Toshiba L200 laptop PC internal hard drive. The 1TB capacity lets your laptop store more pictures, songs and videos, while the low-power profile helps improve battery life. A 128MB cache and advanced cache technology enhance the performance of this Toshiba L200 laptop PC internal hard drive.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Seagate - Barracuda 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6344172/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Seagate</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6344/6344172_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy ample storage space with this Seagate 2TB internal hard drive. The SATA III interface delivers transfer speeds of up to 6Gbps for prompt data access, and the 3.5-inch design fits most desktops without needing an adapter. This Seagate 2TB internal hard drive is compatible with multiple versions of Windows for convenience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Red 1TB Internal SATA NAS Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>64.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>64.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6520452/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6520/6520452_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your system additional storage space with this Western Digital Red Pro 1TB hard drive. Designed to handle business-class data, this rugged device works in medium and large-scale NAS environments and is easy to be integrated into your existing setup. A multi-axis shock sensor keeps this Western Digital Red Pro 1TB hard drive stable and reliable in multi-drive bays.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Black 500GB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Desktops (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>79.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>63.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6520461/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6520/6520461_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This WD Black WD5003AZEX internal hard drive features NoTouch Ramp Load technology, which prevents wear and tear on the drive for increased durability. The 64MB cache buffer offers speedy processing for efficient performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Red 2TB Internal SATA Hard Drive (OEM/Bare Drive)</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6560007/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6560/6560007_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>With 2TB of storage, this WD Red WD20EFRX internal hard drive makes it easy to house your important files on your small NAS system. The Serial ATA interface lets you connect to your Windows or Mac desktop.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Toshiba - 3TB Internal Serial ATA III Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>139.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>139.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/7479294/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Toshiba</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/7479/7479294_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your desktop with this Toshiba internal Serial ATA III hard drive that features a 3TB storage capacity to accommodate your music, movies and more. The internal shock detection and ramp-loading technology help guard against damage.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>j5create - Hard Drive Enclosure for 3.5" SATA Hard Drives - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/8756247/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>j5create</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/8756/8756247_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Expand the storage of your computer with this j5 create JEE351 hard drive enclosure, which allows you to plug a 3.5" SATA hard drive into your computer via a USB 3.0 interface for simple connection. Hot-swap capability enables plug-and-play operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Desktop Everyday 4TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>109.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>109.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9026007/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9026/9026007_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Expand your desktop's storage capabilities with this WD Desktop Everyday SATA hard drive, which features a spacious 4TB capacity to house your movies, music and more. Data transfer rates up to 6 Gbps ensure efficient performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Desktop Everyday 6TB Internal SATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9026016/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.1</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9026/9026016_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Designed for use with select PC and Mac desktops, this WD Desktop Everyday internal SATA hard drive features a 6TB capacity, so you can easily store a wealth of games, movies, music, pictures and other files.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Mainstream 1TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9312067/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9312/9312067_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This WD Mainstream internal Serial ATA hard drive is designed for use with desktops and features data transfer rates up to 6 Gbps for fast performance. The 1TB capacity offers ample space for storing music, movies and more.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Mainstream 2TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>69.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>69.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9312076/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9312/9312076_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your desktop with this WD Mainstream internal Serial ATA hard drive, which features a 64MB cache buffer for rapid processing speed. The 2TB capacity offers space for your documents, music, photos, movies and more.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Mainstream 3TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9312085/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9312/9312085_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>With a generous 3TB capacity, this WD Mainstream internal Serial ATA desktop hard drive easily accommodates your digital media collection. Data transfer rates up to 6 Gbps and a 64MB cache buffer help ensure fast, efficient operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Mainstream 500GB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>44.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>44.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9314108/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9314/9314108_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your laptop a performance boost with this WD Mainstream internal Serial ATA hard drive, which features a spacious 500GB capacity for storing media. Data transfer rates up to 3 Gbps deliver efficient operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Mainstream 1TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Laptops</name>
		<regularPrice>54.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>50.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9314126/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9314/9314126_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Store your important files on this WD Mainstream internal Serial ATA hard drive, which is designed for laptops and features an expansive 1TB capacity to house your media. Low power consumption helps ensure quiet, cool operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - Performance 4TB Internal Serial ATA Hard Drive for Desktops</name>
		<regularPrice>194.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>194.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9315347/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9315/9315347_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This WD Performance internal Serial ATA desktop hard drive features a spacious 4TB capacity, so you can store plenty of movies, songs, photos and other files. Data transfer rates up to 6 Gbps and a 64MB cache offer fast, reliable performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0515000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0504001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>pcmcat270900050001</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>WD - 2TB Internal Hard Drive (NAS)</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/9315443/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>WD</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/9315/9315443_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Designed for use with most NAS systems with up to 5 bays, this WD network hard drive features a spacious 2TB capacity for storing important data. IntelliPower technology delivers reliable performance and minimizes power consumption.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce 8400 GS 1GB GDDR3 PCI Express 2.0 Graphics Card - Silver</name>
		<regularPrice>39.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>39.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1700586/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.2</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1700/1700586_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This graphics card features CUDA technology and DirectX 10 4.0 support for enhanced visual realism. A core clock speed of 520MHz allows high-speed processing.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce 210 1GB DDR3 PCI Express 2.0 Graphics Card - Silver</name>
		<regularPrice>39.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>39.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1700647/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1700/1700647_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This graphics card features 16 processing cores and a 520MHz core clock speed for fast, efficient operation. The DirectX 10.1 and OpenGL 3.1 support provide an ultrarealistic gaming experience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - NVIDIA GeForce GT 710 1GB DDR3 PCI Express 2.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>45.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>45.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4961401/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4961/4961401_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Make your entire PC experience faster with the EVGA GeForce GT 710 dedicated graphics card. Now, you can enjoy better performance in all your PC multimedia applications. Take on modern games with advanced and reliable dedicated graphics. Significantly faster performance than integrated graphics means a rich and smooth gaming experience. Plus, get the power to drive up to three HD displays with a single card.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - NVIDIA GeForce GT 710 VERTO 2GB DDR3 PCI Express 2.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5092306/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5092/5092306_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your video gaming experience with this PNY NVDIA GeForce graphics card. It ups video memory and comes with access to GeForce Experience, which helps you optimize settings and keep up with driver updates. This PNY NVDIA GeForce graphics card has DVI, VGA and HDMI ports to support three HD displays simultaneously.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon R5 220 Core Edition 2GB GDDR3 PCI Express 2.1 Graphics Card - Silver</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5315600/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5315/5315600_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Only at Best BuyEquip your gaming computer with this AMD Radeon GPU. Its PowerTune technology dynamically adjusts the clock speed to provide the optimal performance. With its dual display feature, it enhances your productivity and gaming experience. By utilizing HD 3-D technology, this AMD Radeon GPU with 2GB memory lets you enjoy seamless stereoscopic 3-D gaming.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon R7 240 Core Edition 4GB GDDR3 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>69.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>69.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5315800/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5315/5315800_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Only at Best Buy  Upgrade your gaming computer with this AMD Radeon GPU. Its Graphics Core Next architecture delivers the full visual quality of gaming applications and also has the capabilities of a CPU for overall computer efficiency. Ghost Thermal 2.0 technology facilitates efficient ventilation and cooling in this AMD Radeon GPU to keep up with intense gaming operations.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce GT 710 2GB Single Slot Dual DVI Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>54.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>53.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5597203/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5597/5597203_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy faster and smoother gaming with this EVGA GeForce GT graphics card. With memory bandwidth of 14.4 Gbps, it performs up to 80 percent faster than integrated GPUs. This EVGA GeForce GT graphics card supports up to three HD monitors for easy multitasking with gaming applications and professional design programs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1060 XLR8 Gaming OC Edition 3GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>269.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>202.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5613853/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5613/5613853_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Minimize game-interrupting lags as you eradicate enemies or explore new galaxies with this PNY GeForce Gaming OC graphics card. High-bandwidth GDDR5 technologies and a Dual Fan XLR8 Cooler enhance this plug-and-play card's impressive performance. Immerse yourself in a graphic-heavy game with the clear audio and vivid images that this PNY graphics card delivers.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1050 2GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>174.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>174.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5711723/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5711/5711723_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience seamless gaming visuals with this PNY GeForce GTX 1050 graphics card. It keeps up with the performance requirements of the latest demanding game titles thanks to its NVIDIA Pascal architecture and Game Ready technologies. This PNY GeForce GTX 1050 graphics card has 2GB of GDDR5 RAM, and it supports DirectX 12 for high-performance yet power-efficient operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1070 XLR8 Gaming Edition 8GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>479.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>359.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5838240/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5838/5838240_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your gaming experience with this PNY graphics card. It has 8GB of RAM to maximize bandwidth, producing smooth images, and it's integrated with NVIDIA GameWorks technologies to minimize latency for lifelike game play. This PNY graphics card is fitted with a dual fan cooler to prevent overheating during extended use.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - NVIDIA GeForce GT 1030 2GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>119.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>119.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5901353/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5901/5901353_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your computer's performance with this PNY NVIDIA GeForce graphics card. Its 2GB memory and 1468MHz boost speed provide efficient performance for smooth gaming and video editing, and it supports 4K display devices through its HDMI 2.0 connector. This PNY NVIDIA GeForce graphics card's GeForce Experience software makes driver updates and game optimization easy.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 550 Core Edition 4GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>109.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5982203/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5982/5982203_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Generate stunning game visuals in Full HD with this XFX Radeon RX 550 graphics card. Its 4GB 128-bit memory keeps up with the high-bandwidth requirements of AAA titles, and its XFX True Clock technology optimizes clock speed performance. The AMD FreeSync 2 technology of this FX Radeon RX 550 graphics card lets you enjoy seamless visuals without tears and lags.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1050 Ti GAMING X BV 4GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>209.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>169.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6087802/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6087/6087802_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Equip your gaming rig with this NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1050 graphics card. It has three display outputs, including DisplayPort and HDMI, for connecting monitors and peripherals, and its two large fans force air through the heatsink to keep the processor cool. This NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1050 graphics card has 4GB of RAM for fast image and video rendering.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 580 GTS Black Edition 8GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>259.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>219.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6092641/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.2</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6092/6092641_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your gaming rig with this XFX Radeon graphics card. Its True Clock technology controls clock speed to maximize performance, and the Radeon Chill feature tracks game play to regulate the frame rate to lower temperature and conserve power. The aluminum backplate of this XFX Radeon graphics card protects it while absorbing heat.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 580 GTS XXX Edition 8GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>229.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>229.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6136515/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6136/6136515_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Maximize visual performance of your effects-laden games with this XFX Radeon RX 580 GTS graphics card. Boasting Polaris architecture to make the most of your PCI slot, this upgrade features 4th-generation GCN graphics cores and 8GB of dedicated graphics memory. True Clock technology on this XFX Radeon RX 580 GTS graphics card delivers optimized speeds through its hardware for incredibly high frame rates.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX Vega 56 8GB HBM2 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>799.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>349.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6183041/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>3.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6183/6183041_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade to powerful high-resolution gaming support with this Radeon RX Vega graphics card, which features High-Bandwidth Cache (HBC) to make the most of memory and GPU. This HDMI graphics upgrade has an optimized pixel engine for smooth 3D rendering, while the enhanced polygon geometry engine elevates FPS for more immersive play. With 1471MHz boost clock, this Radeon RX Vega graphics card provides massive support for overclocking.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 560 4GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>149.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6183042/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6183/6183042_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Play the latest in AAA titles with this XFX Radeon RX 560 graphics card. Its power-saving CHILL technology automatically adjusts the frame rate based on in-game movements, and the 4GB of GDDR5 RAM with 1024 stream processors smoothly renders 3D images. This XFX Radeon RX 560 graphics card has DisplayPort and HDMI connections, so it's optimized for large, modern displays.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 570 RS Black Edition 8GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>299.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>299.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6202343/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6202/6202343_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Crank graphics settings on your favorite games up to high with this 8GB XFX Radeon RX 570 graphics card. Its unique Chill power-saving feature dynamically regulates the framerate based on your movements in-game, and it has BIOS-controlled overclocking for optimized performance. This XFX Radeon RX 570 graphics card has a uni-body heatsink to enhance its thermal efficiency, prolonging its life.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - AMD Radeon RX 560 AERO ITX OC 4G GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>149.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>149.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6202776/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6202/6202776_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Up the ante on gaming video with this MSI Aero TX Radeon graphics card. It lets you record in-game video and control overclocking via Android or iOS devices, and it comes with 4GB of dedicated RAM for lag-free performance. This MSI Aero TX Radeon graphics card has solid capacitors for durability under full loads.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - AMD Radeon RX 570 ARMOR OC 8G GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6202778/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6202/6202778_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your current gaming rig with this MSI Armor graphics card. Its 8GB of dedicated memory provides smooth gameplay performance, and its two TORX fans deliver quiet operation and help keep components from overheating. This MSI Armor graphics card has a solid black metal backplate for an extra edge and increased sturdiness.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - AMD Radeon RX 580 ARMOR MK2 OC 8G GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>239.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>239.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6202779/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6202/6202779_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your gaming machine with this MSI Radeon Armor MK2 graphics card. The TORX 2.0 fan is super quiet, so you won't be distracted during battles, and the double ball bearings keep the motors running for years of use. This MSI Radeon Armor MK2 graphics card has 8GB of dedicated RAM and an Afterburner overclocking capability that supports multi-GPU setups.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 580 GTS Black Core Edition 8GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>239.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>221.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6217300/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6217/6217300_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Ramp up the gaming capabilities on your computer with Radeon RX 580 Series graphics. XFX True Clock technology optimizes clock speeds based on performance needs, keeping you in the action in each frame, while Radeon CHILL technology lowers power consumption and maximizes framerate potential. The custom aluminum backplate design on this Radeon RX 580 Series graphics card protects your GPU from overheating.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - GeForce RTX 2080 Ti Gaming X Trio 11GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>1309.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>1309.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290652/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.1</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290652_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your favorite games with this NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 graphics card. It has 8GB of dedicated video memory for smooth rendering at favorable frame rates, and the vapor chamber cooling technology facilitates efficient heat dissipation. This NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1080 graphics card is compatible with VR hardware for an immersive gaming experience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - GeForce RTX 2080 Gaming X Trio 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>779.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>689.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290654/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290654_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Design an invincible gaming rig with this MSI GeForce RTX GAMING X TRIO graphics card. Its Tri-Frozr thermal system utilizes three TORX 3.0 fans with double ball bearings for maximum quiet cooling, and customizable RGB lights add stunning effects. This MSI GeForce RTX GAMING X TRIO graphics card has 8GB of GDDR6 memory, rendering HDR visuals at peak frame rates.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2080 Ti XC Ultra Gaming 11GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>1249.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>1249.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290657/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290657_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Equip your gaming rig with this EVGA GeForce RTX graphics card. It's powered by NVIDIA's Turing architecture that provides increased gaming realism and speed, and it has advanced overclocking capabilities that let you crank game settings up to the highest levels for more detail. This EVGA GeForce RTX graphics card has a built-in cooling system that keeps components from overheating.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2080 XC Ultra Gaming 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>849.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>719.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290660/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290660_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Equip your PC for next-generation gaming with this EVGA GeForce RTX XC Ultra graphics card. The real-time ray tracing and AI functions of its NVIDIA Turing architecture provide striking realism, and dual hydrodynamic bearing fans maintain a cool system. This VR-ready EVGA GeForce RTX XC Ultra graphics card has 8GB of GDDR6 memory for seamless display of complex visuals.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2070 XC Ultra Gaming 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans &amp; RGB LED</name>
		<regularPrice>599.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>479.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290661/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290661_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>The EVGA GeForce RTX 20-series graphics cards are powered by the all-new NVIDIA Turing architecture to give you incredible new levels of gaming realism, speed, power efficiency, and immersion. With the EVGA GeForce RTX 20-series gaming cards, you get a perfect gaming experience with next-generation graphics performance, ice-cold cooling, and advanced overclocking features with the all-new EVGA Precision X1 software.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2080 Ti XC GAMING 11GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans &amp; RGB LED</name>
		<regularPrice>1199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>1199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290663/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290663_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Maintain the velocity of your gaming experience with this NVIDIA EVGA GeForce RTX graphic card. Its Turing architecture increases the level of power, authenticity and pace during games, and the AI enhanced graphics create an immersive experience. This EVGA GeForce RTX graphic card lets you play without fear of overheating thanks to its advanced cooling technologies.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2080 XC GAMING 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans &amp; RGB LED</name>
		<regularPrice>799.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>799.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290681/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290681_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your gaming experience with this NVIDIA EVGA GeForce RTX graphics card. Its 8 GB of GDDR6 RAM and NVIDIA's RTX architecture provide top-shelf gaming performance, and the dual-slot configuration helps promote better airflow for stable performance. This NVIDIA EVGA GeForce RTX graphics card supports real-time ray tracing for a new level of realism in your games.&amp;#13;</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2070 XC Gaming 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans &amp; RGB LED</name>
		<regularPrice>579.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>539.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290682/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.1</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290682_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Discover the ultimate in graphics with this EVGA GeForce RTX 2070 graphics card. Real-time ray tracing creates ever-more realistic gaming environments, powered by the NVIDIA Turing architecture, and EVGA Precision X1 software delivers powerful overclocking so you can get even more out of your machine. This EVGA GeForce RTX 2070 graphics card ensures quiet but efficient operation with the precision fan blades and hub.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - GeForce RTX 2080 Ti XLR8 Gaming Overclocked Edition 11GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Silver/Gray</name>
		<regularPrice>1299.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>1299.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290686/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290686_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Immerse yourself in adventures with this PNY GeForce RTX 2080 gaming graphics card. Its NVIDIA Turing technology provides AI-enabled enhancements and real-time ray tracing to create stunning images, and the special overclocked edition features improve the boost clock speed to 1545MHz. This PNY GeForce RTX 2080 gaming graphics card has 8GB of GDDR6 memory for realistic 4K and VR scenes.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - GeForce RTX 2080 XLR8 Gaming Overclocked Edition 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>849.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>829.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6290690/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6290/6290690_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Generate lifelike environments with this PNY GeForce RTX XLR8 gaming graphics card. It has 8GB of GDDR6 memory for a seamless 4K and VR experience, and the NVIDIA Turing architecture uses real-time ray tracing and AI-enabled enhancements to produce hyperrealistic visuals. This overclocked-edition PNY GeForce RTX XLR8 gaming graphics card provides powerful performance with a boost clock speed of 1710MHz.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>NVIDIA - GeForce RTX 2080 Ti Founders Edition 11GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>1199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>1199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6291646/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.1</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>NVIDIA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6291/6291646_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your gaming experience with this NVIDIA GeForce RTX graphics card. Its Turing architecture uses all-new technologies that create incredibly lifelike graphics, and the 11GB of GDDR6 memory allows for smoother and faster gameplay. This NVIDIA GeForce RTX graphics card lets you take screenshots and share experiences with your friends.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>NVIDIA - GeForce RTX 2080 Founders Edition 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>799.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>699.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6291648/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>NVIDIA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6291/6291648_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enhance your gaming experience with this NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 graphics card. Its Turing CPU architecture has six times the performance capability of older versions for exceptional realism, speed, power efficiency and immersion. This NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 graphics card has a next-generation eight-phase power supply for maximum overclocking to power your central processing unit.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>NVIDIA - GeForce RTX 2070 Founders Edition 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.1 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>599.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>479.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6291650/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>NVIDIA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6291/6291650_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Heighten your gaming experience with this VR-ready NVIDIA GeForce RTX Founders Edition graphics card. The NVIDIA Turing architecture incorporates real-time ray tracing and AI features for enhanced realism, and the 8GB of memory supports peak resolutions and frame rates. Dual-axial 13-blade fans and a vapor chamber keep this NVIDIA GeForce RTX Founders Edition graphics card cool and quiet.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - GeForce RTX 2070 GAMING Z 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>549.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>479.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6291651/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6291/6291651_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Take your gaming to the next level with this NVIDIA GeForce graphics card. Its 8GB RAM and RTX processing unit keep even the most demanding games running smoothly, while VR support provides a high level of immersion for virtual-reality gaming titles. This NVIDIA GeForce graphics card can handle up to four monitors with a base clock speed of 1410MHz.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - XLR8 Gaming NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2070 Overclocked Edition 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Red</name>
		<regularPrice>589.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>549.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6300813/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6300/6300813_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience immersive gaming with this GeForce RTX 2070 graphics card. Its real-time ray tracing and AI technology swiftly render realistic game worlds, and NVIDIA G-Sync powers 240Hz refresh rates for smooth gameplay. Adapted to virtual reality, this GeForce RTX 2070 graphics card lets you enjoy lifelike experiences in 4K resolution.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 590 Fatboy OC+ 8GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>279.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>249.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6315898/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6315/6315898_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience the exceptional visuals of top PC games with this VR-ready XFX Radeon RX Fatboy graphics card. Its 8GB of 256-bit GDDR5 memory handles the demands of complex gaming and 4K streaming, and the 1600MHz overclocking capability provides an extra performance boost. This XFX Radeon RX Fatboy graphics card stays cool and efficient with an increased heat sink surface area.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>ASUS - NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2080 OC Edition 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>869.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>829.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6319232/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>ASUS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6319/6319232_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Begin your gaming adventures with this ROG Strix GeForce RTX graphics card. The overclocked edition delivers powerful performance to help you crush the competition, and the axial-tech fans and MaxContact technology ensure efficient thermal management. This VR-ready ROG Strix GeForce RTX graphics card is compatible with 4K displays for maximum immersion.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>NVIDIA - TITAN RTX 24GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>2499.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>2499.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6320585/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>NVIDIA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6320/6320585_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Get through projects without screen lag or stutter by using this NVIDIA TITAN RTX graphics card. It has 24GB of GDDR6 memory to deliver blazing speeds, and Turing technology delivers up to six times the performance of older graphics cards to support memory-intensive programs. This NVIDIA TITAN RX graphics card also provides the power of AI and ray tracing.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce RTX 2060 XC Ultra Gaming 6GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans</name>
		<regularPrice>429.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>379.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6321301/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6321/6321301_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Give your gaming setup a powerful upgrade with this EVGA GeForce RTX 2060 XC ultra gaming graphics card. The built-in fans keep your computer running cool throughout intense play sessions, and the real-time ray tracing delivers faithful, realistic image rendering. This EVGA GeForce RTX 2060 XC ultra gaming graphics card features NVIDIA GPU Boost for fast frame rates and smooth playback.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - GeForce RTX 2060 GAMING Z 6GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Silver/Black</name>
		<regularPrice>399.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>399.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6322052/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6322/6322052_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience games like never before with this MSI NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2060 Gaming Z graphics card. Featuring real-time ray tracing technology, NVIDIA Turing architecture improves graphical quality with realistic lighting, shadows and reflections. This MSI NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2060 Gaming Z graphics card stays cool during intense sessions with an MSI TWIN FROZR thermal design.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - GeForce GTX 1660 Ti Gaming X 6GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>319.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>304.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6330461/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6330/6330461_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Run demanding games at high frame rates and in incredible detail with this MSI GeForce GTX 1660 Ti graphics card. Games, streaming and other graphical programs run fluidly thanks to the 1,536 CUDA cores, and three DisplayPort outputs make multi-monitor setup simple. This MSI GeForce GTX 1660 Ti graphics card has 6GB of memory for handling intense workloads.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce GTX 1660 Ti XC Ultra Gaming 6GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans</name>
		<regularPrice>319.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>319.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6330848/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6330/6330848_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Upgrade your gaming PC with this EVGA GeForce GTX 1660 Ti XC Ultra GAMING graphics card. Featuring 1536 CUDA cores and 6144MB of high-performance DDR6 memory, this graphics card easily handles demanding titles at high settings. This EVGA GeForce 1660 Ti XC Ultra GAMING graphics card is compatible with NVIDIA G-SYNC and supports Microsoft DirectX 12 for high-powered gaming.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon VII 16GB HBM2 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card</name>
		<regularPrice>699.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>699.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6330849/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6330/6330849_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Step up your game with this XFX AMD Radeon VII graphics card. The 16GB of HBM2 memory and up to 1TB/sec. of memory bandwidth easily handle the most visually intensive titles. This XFV AMD Radeon VII graphics card renders delivers smooth gameplay and realistic images with 3,840 stream processors and a 4096-bit memory interface.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce GTX 1660 XC Black Gaming 6GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with HDB Fan</name>
		<regularPrice>229.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>218.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6339195/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6339/6339195_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Handle demanding PC games with this EVGA GeForce GTX 1660 XC graphics card. The EVGA cooling system uses a hydraulic-dynamic bearing fan and heat skink with L-shaped fins for enhanced thermal stability. With NVIDIA Turing architecture and 6GB of memory, this EVGA GeForce GTX 1660 XC graphics card renders complex visuals seamlessly.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - GeForce GTX 1660 XC Ultra Gaming 6GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card with Dual HDB Fans</name>
		<regularPrice>259.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>259.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6339197/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6339/6339197_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Run games and other graphically intense applications smoothly with this EVGA GeForce GTX 1660 XC graphics card. The 6144MB of GDDR5 RAM deliver the resources needed for high frame rates and fluid motion. This EVGA GeForce GTX 1660 XC graphics card is G-SYNC-ready to prevent screen tearing and stuttering for a high-quality experience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660 6GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black/Gray</name>
		<regularPrice>249.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>249.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6343050/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6343/6343050_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience incredible visuals with this MSI GeForce GTX 1660 Gaming X 6G graphics card. Two Torx fans and a heatsink with advanced aerodynamics provide state-of-the-art cooling to this NVIDIA-powered card during heated gaming sessions. A custom PCB enhances power delivery make this MSI GeForce GTX 1660 Gaming X 6G graphics card a strong performer in even the most demanding games.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - XLR8 Gaming NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1660 Overclocked Edition 6GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>249.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>249.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6343702/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6343/6343702_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy high-end gaming with this PNY GeForce GTX 1660 XLR8 graphics card. The 6GB of GDDR5 memory offer rapid access to relevant data, and multi-screen support delivers an immersive experience. This PNY GeForce GTX 1660 XLR8 graphics card features game-ready drivers and is VR-compatible for excellent performance with current and future applications.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - XLR8 NVIDIA GeForce GTX 1650 Overclocked Edition 4GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6343714/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.4</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6343/6343714_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy high-end gaming with this PNY GeForce GTX 1650 overclocked graphics card. The NVIDIA Turing architecture offers excellent performance with old and current games, while the GDDR5 memory delivers high frame rates. This PNY GeForce GTX 1650 overclocked graphics card supports dual-monitor setups for an increase in workspace and an immersive experience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>PNY - XLR8 Gaming NVIDIA GeForce RTX 2060 Overclocked Edition 6GB GDDR6 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>379.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>379.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6346830/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>PNY</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6346/6346830_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Step up gaming performance with this PNY GeForce RTX 2060 graphics card. The T uring architecture offers real-time ray tracing and utilizes the power of AI for next-level visuals. VR Ready technology supports current and next-gen titles for lasting performance. This PNY GeForce RTX 2060 graphics card features HDMI, DisplayPort and DVI-D ports for multi-screen support, providing an immersive experience.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>MSI - GeForce GTX 1650 Gaming X 4GB GDDR5 PCI Express 3.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6347252/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.2</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>MSI</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6347/6347252_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience incredible visuals with this MSI GeForce GTX 1650 graphics card. The DisplayPort and HDMI ports offer multiple connection options and multi-monitor use for increased productivity. NVIDIA G-SYNC technology provides smooth tear-free graphics with up to 240Hz refresh rate for responsiveness. This MSI GeForce GTX 1650 graphics card uses 4GB of dedicated GDDR5 memory, rendering high-resolution textures easily.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 5700 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 4.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>349.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>349.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6358880/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6358/6358880_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy immersive visuals on your PC games with this AMD Radeon RX 5700 graphics card. The 8GB of GDDR6 memory keeps up with the demands of 3-D media streaming and virtual reality games. This AMD Radeon RX 5700 graphics features a max 1725MHz overclocking capability for a performance boost, and the DisplayPort and HDMI ports provide flexible connectivity options.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507002</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>XFX - AMD Radeon RX 5700XT 8GB GDDR6 PCI Express 4.0 Graphics Card - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>399.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>399.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6358893/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.3</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>XFX</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6358/6358893_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience the exceptional visuals of top PC games with this XFX Radeon RX 5700 XT graphics card. Its 8GB of 256-bit GDDR6 memory handles the demands of complex gaming and 4K streaming, and the 1905MHz overclocking capability provides an extra performance boost.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 500W ATX12V / EPS12V 80 Plus Bronze Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>49.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>49.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/1017256/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/1017/1017256_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Deliver up to 500W of continuous power to your computer with this EVGA 500 Bronze 100-B1-0500-KR power supply that features 80PLUS Bronze certification for efficient performance. Heavy-duty protections help ensure safe operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Antec - 450-Watt Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>39.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>39.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4070566/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Antec</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4070/4070566_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Get effective power and quiet cooling performance with this Antec 450-watt power supply that features heavy-duty circuitry protection on all rails to help prevent damage from a variety of dangers.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - HXi Series 1200W ATX 80 Plus Platinum Fully Modular Power Supply</name>
		<regularPrice>269.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>269.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895507/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895507_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>When you want to install multiple high-power graphics cards, only the Corsair HXi 1200 W power supply will do. Virtually silent operation and incredible cooling reduces the stress on your system, yet its high-performance design makes upgrading your system a breeze. Use the Corsair Link Dashboard application with this Corsair 1200 W power supply for absolute control over its settings.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - HXi Series 850W ATX 80 Plus Platinum Fully Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895513/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895513_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Get a power supply that is worthy of your computer with the CORSAIR HX850i power supply. Designed to work in high-performance systems that draw up to 850 W of power, this power supply ensures maximum reliability and reduces the strain on the motherboard. The CORSAIR HX850i power supply helps even out surges and spikes for easy protection.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - RMi Series 850W ATX 80 Plus Gold Fully Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>159.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>159.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895533/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895533_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Save money on your next power bill with the CORSAIR RM Series power supply. Built with low-noise capacitors, its whisper-quiet running is won't disturb when in use. The system's high-quality components ensure continuous power. CORSAIR RM Series power supplies feature low-profile cables that are modular so you can accommodate your exact needs.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - RMi Series 1000W ATX 80 Plus Gold Fully Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>199.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/4895534/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/4895/4895534_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build your computer with confidence by using this CORSAIR PC power supply. Built using Japanese capacitors, the 80 PLUS Gold certification ensures your computer operates with reduced heat and minimal sound. CORSAIR's unique design also allows desktop control of the fan speed. Bring power to your PC with this CORSAIR PC power supply.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 850W Modular BQ Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>119.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>119.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5594501/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5594/5594501_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your customized desktop computer with this EVGA power supply. The large built-in fan prevents it from overheating during heavy use, and the sturdy box construction makes it easy to mount externally or install in your computer shell. This EVGA power supply comes with all the cords needed for installation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 650W ATX Modular GQ Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>99.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5597200/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5597/5597200_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Operate your computer system efficiently with this EVGA GQ power supply. Its 135mm fan operates quietly and only when needed thanks to its power-saving ECO mode. The modular interface of this 80 Plus Gold-certified EVGA GQ power supply provides flexibility in cabling options for improved airflow, convenience and working efficiency.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 750W Modular P2 Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>159.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>147.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5597201/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5597/5597201_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your custom-built desktop computer with this 750W EVGA SuperNova power supply. The built-in fan keeps your components cool with little noise, and modular cabling keeps cords and wires neat. This EVGA SuperNova power supply is platinum-rated for efficiency, so it keeps your computer running at top speed without creating excessive heat.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 1000W ATX12V / EPS12V GQ Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>179.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>150.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5622831/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5622/5622831_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Experience 90 percent efficiency under typical loads with this EVGA power supply. It supports multiple NVIDIA graphics cards so you can enjoy the latest games in vivid detail. Enjoy silent operation under low to medium loads with the ECO mode feature. This EVGA power supply has a semi-modular configuration to facilitate airflow and reduce cable clutter.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 650W Modular BQ Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>74.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>74.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5622832/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5622/5622832_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Keep your computer running with this EVGA power supply. It supplies 650W of output to give your gadgets the juice they need, and its ECO mode provides control over performance and efficiency. This EVGA power supply has a quiet 140mm cooling fan for safe operation, and its modular cables reduce clutter.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 850W ATX12V / EPS12V 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>159.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>159.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5622834/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5622/5622834_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Enjoy silent operation with this EVGA power supply. The ECO mode prevents the fan from running during low to medium loads, activating it only when needed, and the high-quality capacitors deliver 90 percent efficiency under typical loads. This EVGA power supply accommodates multiple NVIDIA graphics cards for high-performance gaming in stunning detail.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 850W ATX12V / EPS12V Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>159.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>159.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5708601/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5708/5708601_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Support your high-performance computer system with this EVGA SuperNova G3 power supply. Its hydraulic dynamic bearing fan operates quietly and provides outstanding longevity, and a fully modular design provides setup flexibility. This 80 Plus Gold-certified EVGA SuperNova G3 has an 850W power supply to handle maximum loads from multiple components efficiently.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 550W ATX12V / EPS12V Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>99.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5753404/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5753/5753404_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Operate your computer system efficiently with this EVGA SuperNova G3 power supply. It has an ECO mode that provides quiet operation for low to medium loads, and its 550W rating keeps up with the maximum performance of your gaming components. This 80 Plus Gold-certified EVGA SuperNova G3 power supply comes with a heavy-duty circuit protection system to prevent surges.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 1000W ATX12V / EPS12V 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>249.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>249.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5753406/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5753/5753406_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Provide powerful support for your extreme gaming system with this EVGA power supply. Its 1000W rating handles the power requirements of your computer and its multiple components at their maximum performance, and its heavy-duty protection system provides operation safety. This compact EVGA power supply is 80 Plus Gold-certified with reliable efficiency even at higher loads.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 750W ATX12V / EPS12V Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5753407/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5753/5753407_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Provide reliable current for your gaming computer and components with this EVGA power supply. Its high-quality Japanese capacitors with 750W rating provide ample power handling of your computer&amp;#8217;s peak performance, and it runs quietly in ECO mode during low to medium loads. This EVGA power supply lets you customize wiring installations with its fully modular design.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 650W ATX12V / EPS12V Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>109.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>102.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5753408/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5753/5753408_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Secure your gaming rig and components with this EVGA SuperNova G3 power supply. It's 80 Plus Gold-certified for optimal operating efficiency, and its fully modular design provides flexible cabling setup for enhanced airflow. This 650W EVGA SuperNova G3 power supply operates quietly and has improved longevity thanks to the hydraulic dynamic bearing fan.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - CX-M Series 650W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Bronze Modular Power Supply - Matte black</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>79.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5845214/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5845/5845214_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your custom-built computer with this CORSAIR power supply. It's built for efficient operation, so it saves energy and doesn&amp;#8217;t produce much heat, and it operates quietly at slow and medium speeds for a better work environment. The modular cable system of this CORSAIR power supply provides easy, clutter-free installation in compatible ATX desktop cases.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - HX Series 1200W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Platinum Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>239.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>239.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5885000/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5885/5885000_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power your high-performance computer with this CORSAIR HX Series fully modular power supply. It has overvoltage and undervoltage protection to keep your PC safe, and its fan only speeds up when it needs to, ensuring quiet operation. This CORSAIR HX Series fully modular power supply has 105-degree Celsius capacitors for reliability.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Insignia - 550W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Bronze Power Supply - Gray</name>
		<regularPrice>54.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>34.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5974702/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Insignia</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5974/5974702_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Add this Insignia power supply to your next desktop computer build. It delivers 550W RMS of stable, continuous power for your system, and its thermostat-controlled 120mm fan runs quietly, so it won't interfere with indoor activities. This Insignia power supply has short circuit defense and overvoltage protection for added safety.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Insignia - 450W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Power Supply - Gray</name>
		<regularPrice>44.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>44.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/5976300/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Insignia</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/5976/5976300_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Keep your computer running well with this Insignia power supply. It produces 450W for better game and program performance, and its short circuit and over/under voltage protection prevent surges from harming your electronic devices. This Insignia power supply has a thermostat-controlled, low-noise fan to regulate temperatures without causing any disturbances.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - RMx Series 1000W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>189.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>189.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6073500/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6073/6073500_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Run your high-performance PC with this CORSAIR RMx power supply. It&amp;#8217;s made with Japanese 105 degree C capacitors for solid durability, and its Zero RPM fan mode provides optimal cooling and quiet operation for low-to-medium loads. This 80 PLUS Gold-certified CORSAIR RMx power supply comes with a fully modular cable set for efficient, clutter-free installation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Thermaltake - SMART PRO RGB 750W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>89.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6088103/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.5</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Thermaltake</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6088/6088103_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Maintain the optimal temperature of your machine with this Thermaltake fan. Designed to increase static pressure, the fan blade pushes out weaker air to pressurize the air, and the anti-vibration mounting system minimizes movement during use for stability. This Thermaltake fan has a face-up design, so you can see the RGB lights.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Thermaltake - ToughPower Grand RGB 1200W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Platinum Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>219.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>219.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6196403/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Thermaltake</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6196/6196403_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Handle intense computing with this 1200W Thermaltake Toughpower Grand power supply. Its 80 PLUS Platinum certification ensures solid, energy-efficient performance, and its fan with concentrated compression blades and anti-vibration mounting system provides optimal, low-noise cooling. The RGB LED ring of this fully modular Thermaltake Toughpower Grand power supply has five lighting modes for an enhanced aesthetic.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Thermaltake - ToughPower Grand RGB 850W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>127.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6200000/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Thermaltake</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6200/6200000_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Run your custom desktop with this 80 PLUS Gold-rated Thermaltake Toughpower Grand power supply. Its fully modular design enables a flexible, space-efficient cabling setup, and its customizable RGB LED ring makes it visually distinct. The hydraulic bearing fan of this 850W Thermaltake Toughpower Grand power supply has an anti-vibration mounting system for quiet operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 650W 80 Plus Gold Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>109.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>94.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6204517/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6204/6204517_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Equip your custom-built desktop computer with stable power using this 650W EVGA power supply. It's fully modular and has an uncluttered internal layout that improves airflow, and its fluid dynamic bearings result in a quieter, longer-lasting fan. The smaller size of this 80 Plus Gold certified EVGA power supply provides more space without compromising performance.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 1000W ATX /EPS 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>199.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>159.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6209800/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.8</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6209/6209800_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build a? computer? system your way with the EVGA Supernova power supply. Small but mighty, it provides a reliable power source with a small footprint that leaves space for additional components in your computer case. The EVGA Supernova features fluid bearings for quiet performance and uses authentic Japanese capacitors for a long and reliable life.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - RMx Series 850W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>139.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>139.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6229601/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6229/6229601_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build an efficient, high-performance computer with this 850W Corsair RMx power supply unit. Its industrial-grade Japanese capacitors ensure solid power delivery, and it's fully modular for flexible configuration. Set this 80 PLUS Gold-rated Corsair RMx power supply unit on zero fan mode for quiet operation during low and medium loads.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - RMx Series 750W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>129.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>129.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6229604/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6229/6229604_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Support your custom desktop with this 750W Corsair RMx power supply. It has an 80 PLUS Gold efficiency rating for lower power consumption, and its 100 percent Japanese capacitors provide long-lasting performance. This fully modular Corsair RMx power supply lets you set up a tidy computer hardware system with plenty of power.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Thermaltake - SMART 700W ATX12V 2.3 80 Plus Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6231802/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Thermaltake</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6231/6231802_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Build an efficient desktop computer with this 700W Thermaltake smart power supply. Its high 80 percent efficiency rate provides energy-saving operations, and its single +12V rail design lets you achieve stable, reliable performance for long hours of usage. This Thermaltake smart power supply has an intelligent 120m cooling fan that delivers low noise level operations.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>GAMDIAS - 750W ATX12V 2.2 80 Plus Bronze Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>84.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>84.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6304830/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>GAMDIAS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6304/6304830_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Delight gamers with the silent operation and high efficiency of this Gamdias power supply. Its fan lies face up for efficient cooling, and it displays one of 26 multicolored lighting effects at the touch of a button. Enjoy the quiet, reliable operation and comprehensive protection of this Gamdias power supply.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>GAMDIAS - 1200W ATX12V 2.4/EPS12V 2.92 80 Plus Platinum Modular Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>279.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>230.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6304831/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>5.0</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>GAMDIAS</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6304/6304831_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Reclaim efficiency and boost control with this 80 PLUS Platinum Gamdias Cyclops power supply. It lets you combine multiple GPUs for even stronger operations during game play, and the Japanese capacitors stabilize conductivity for a smooth flow. This Gamdias Cyclops power supply lets you place the fan face-up to improve ventilation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Cooler Master - MWE Gold 750W ATX12V 2.31 80 Plus Gold Modular Power Supply DC-DC Technology - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>119.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>119.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6333805/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Cooler Master</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6333/6333805_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Protect your computer from over current and short circuits with this Cooler Master MWE gold full-modular power supply. Full-modular cable management improves airflow and minimizes clutter in the chassis, while a whisper-quiet Silencio fan with LDB bearings ensures longer service life. This Cooler Master MWE gold full-modular power supply features DC-to-DC and synchronous technologies for reliability and stability.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Thermaltake - SMART 700W ATX 80 Plus Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6339087/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.9</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Thermaltake</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6339/6339087_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Power up gaming desktops with this Thermaltake Smart power supply. A continuous 700W power output keeps demanding computer setups energized, while the industry-grade power, voltage and short-circuit protections safeguard sensitive components. This Thermaltake Smart power supply has an embedded 120mm cooling fan that disperses heat efficiently without producing distracting noise.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 700W ATX12V /EPS12V 80 Plus Bronze Power Supply DC-DC Technology - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>79.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>79.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/6346160/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.6</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/6346/6346160_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Develop a high-performance computer and support high-end graphics cards with this 700W EVGA 700BR power supply. Heavy-duty protections help keep delicate electronics safe, while the intelligent automatic fan offers near-silent performance. This 80 PLUS Bronze-certified EVGA 700BR power supply reduces electricity use, and active power-factor correction minimizes interference for increased efficiency and reliability.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>CORSAIR - CX Series Modular CX750M 750W 80 Plus Bronze ATX Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>99.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>89.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/8324202/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>CORSAIR</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/8324/8324202_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This Corsair CX Series Modular CX750M CP-9020061-NA power supply features over- and under-voltage, over-power and short-circuit protection to prevent damage to your components. The flexible modular cabling system accommodates your system configuration.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>EVGA - 600W ATX 12V/EPS 12V 80 Plus Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>59.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>59.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/8511029/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>EVGA</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/8511/8511029_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>Create a functional, efficient computer by adding this 600W EVGA 80 PLUS 100-W1-0600-K1 ATX 12V/EPS 12V power supply to your custom build. An ultraquiet, intelligent auto fan cools components without generating much noise during operation.</longDescription>
	</products>
	<products>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>cat00000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0500000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507000</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<categoryPath>
			<id>abcat0507009</id>
		</categoryPath>
		<name>Thermaltake - Smart Series 650W ATX 12V v2.3/EPS 12V 80 Plus Power Supply - Black</name>
		<regularPrice>69.99</regularPrice>
		<salePrice>69.99</salePrice>
		<url>https://api.bestbuy.com/click/-/8733872/pdp</url>
		<customerReviewAverage>4.7</customerReviewAverage>
		<manufacturer>Thermaltake</manufacturer>
		<image>https://img.bbystatic.com/BestBuy_US/images/products/8733/8733872_sa.jpg</image>
		<longDescription>This Thermaltake SMART Series SP-650P power supply delivers 650W maximum output and 780W peak output and supports Intel&amp;#174; ATX 12V v2.3 and EPS 12V standards. A 120mm fan with intelligent temperature control cools your components.</longDescription>
	</products>
</info>